&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：你们中的一些人可能在想，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Some of you may be wondering,
那么箭头函数呢？
well what about arrow functions?
我们在ES6中添加的最受欢迎的功能谁知道有多久了，
That favorite feature that we've added to ES6 for who knows how long,
我的意思是谁知道人们已经要求这个箭头功能多久了，但是
I mean who knows how long people have been asking for this arrow function, but
它终于在ES6着陆了。
it finally landed in ES6.
我喜欢想象也许Brendan Ike想要这么做
I like to imagine that maybe Brendan Ike wanted to do that
在最初的原型中，他花了15年左右的时间。
in the original prototypes, and it just took him 15 years or whatever.
但是箭头功能在几年前的第六年就出现了。
But arrow functions arrived in year six a few years back.
就好像乌云敞开，天空照耀着我们，如果你愿意，
And it is as if the clouds opened and heaven shone down upon us, if you will,
人们似乎进入了新的启蒙阶段
that people just seemed to move to this new level of enlightenment and
爱和喜悦的语言，一旦他们得到了箭头的功能。
love and joy for the language once they got the arrow function.
你可以在这里看到第1行，数学中箭头函数的用法，
You see here on line 1, the usage of an arrow function in the math,
与名称函数表达式相反。
as opposed to a name function expression.
所以你在想，嘿，凯尔，你对箭头功能有什么感觉？
So you're wondering, hey Kyle, what's your feeling about arrow functions?
我的回答是，箭头函数是匿名的。
And my response is, arrow functions are anonymous.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：我认为不应该使用匿名函数表达式，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: I don't think you should use anonymous function expressions,
我觉得你能算出来。
I think you can do the math.
我认为你不应该使用箭头函数。
I don't think you ought to be using arrow functions.
当然，我认为您不应该使用箭头函数作为一般功能
Certainly I don't think you should be using arrow functions as a general
替换所有其他功能。
replacement for all other functions.
你不应该仅仅因为它们漂亮、简短、简洁的语法而使用它们。
You shouldn't be using them just because they're nice and short, concise syntax.
这不是创造它们的原因，这只是它们的特征之一
That isn't why they were created, that's only one of the characteristics
也许我认为可以争辩的甚至不是主要特征。
that maybe I think could be argued not even the primary characteristic.
顺便说一下句法越短，
The shorter the syntax by the way,
语法的拐角情况越复杂。
the more complex the corner cases of syntax are.
如果你曾经为各种不同的案件争论不休，
And if you've ever wrangled various different corner cases,
箭头函数语法类似于15种不同的变体。
there is like 15 different variations on the arrow function syntax.
所以不是没有代价的。
So doesn't come without a cost.
但我要告诉你，看第一行的唯一方法就是
But I would tell you that the only way looking at line 1 that you can figure out
error函数所做的是读取它的函数体。
what that error function is doing, is to read it's function body.
但是当我读取函数名时，我不需要读取任何代码。
But when I read the function name I don't need to read any code.
那里有一个英文名字告诉我这个函数的用途。
There's one English name there that tells me the purpose of that function.
很多人跟我争论说，
A lot of people argue with me and say,
第1行上的箭头函数是完全自明的。
the arrow function on line 1 is completely self obvious.
也许这是不言而喻的，但它仍然是一个推论。
Maybe it is self obvious, but it is still an inference.
你仍然需要从代码中推断出这样做的目的，
You are still having to infer the purpose of that from the code,
而不是把目的列出来。
rather than seeing the purpose listed out.
如果我给出一个更好的名字，我就是在节省幻灯片上的空间。
And if I gave an even better name, I was saving space on the slides.
但如果我给出一个更好的名字，比如get person id或get default person id。
But if I gave an even better name like get person ID or get default person id.
我可以把更多的信息放在里面，从语义上告诉读者
I can put lots of more information in there that semantically tells the reader
我的代码的目的是什么，在代码中不会很明显。
of my code what its purpose is, that would not be obvious in the code.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：所以，我的看法是，不要为此使用箭头函数。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So, my take is, don't use arrow functions for this purpose.
在本课程的稍后部分，我们将回到箭头函数，您将看到一个和
Later in the course we will come back to arrow functions and you'll see the one and
对于箭头函数规则，我只有一个例外，
only one exception that I have to the arrow functions rule,
这是他们的词汇这一行为。
which is their lexical this behavior.
但我不支持或推荐或
But I do not endorse or recommend or
建议使用它们作为任何功能的通用替代。
suggest using them as a general replacement for any function.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：短还是长？
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Short or long?
另一个例子，如果你做过承诺链，我不是一个承诺的狂热粉丝
Another example, if you've done promise chains, I'm not a big fan of promise
无论如何，链条，但如果你喜欢做承诺链条，
chains anyway, but if you like to do promise chains,
这是您通常只解析这些函数的另一种情况。
this is another case where you often will just parse in these functions.
这是其中一个地方，尽管我之前被问过，
Here's one of these places where even though, that I was asked earlier,
我可能会倾向于我的规则，因为这是第14行的一条直线。
I might tend for my rule because this is a one liner on line 14.
我可能倾向于将其作为内联函数表达式，
I might tend to do that as an inline function expression,
因为我真的很不喜欢承诺链的可读性。
because I really dislike the readability of promise chain so much.
我发现它们很难阅读，而且很像意大利面条，非常像jQuery
I find them very hard to read and very spaghetti-ish, very much like the jQuery
每个人都说我们几年前不应该做的代码。
code that everybody said we shouldn't be doing several years back.
我发现承诺链也是同样的风格。
I find promise chains to be in that same style.
我以前很喜欢那种风格，现在我非常不喜欢那种风格，
And I used to be in love with that style, and now I very much dislike that style,
主要从可读性的角度来看。
from a readability perspective primarily.
所以即使我通常有一个规则，我会将它作为内联传递
So even though I might normally have a rule where I would pass it as an inline
函数表达式。
function expression.
在这种情况下，
In this particular case,
我可能会将该函数作为函数声明提取出来，并且
I would probably pull that function out as a function declaration, and
因此，承诺链将具有类似于您在第11行中看到的内容，
therefore the promise chain would have something like you see on line 11,
它通过名称引用函数，而不是完全引用函数表达式。
which is referencing a function by name, instead of a function expression at all.
但是我仍然不会像你在第10行看到的那样使用箭头函数。
But I still wouldn't use the arrow function like you see on line 10.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：现在，有些人说，嗯，他们是匿名的，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Now, some people have said, well, they're anonymous,
但您仍然可以将它们赋值给变量和
but you can still assign them to variables and
从他们身上得到几乎相同的好处，对吧？
get almost the same benefit out of them, right?
我可以获取这个getId并为它分配一个名为getId的变量，然后
I can take this getId and assign it a variable called getId, and
那我就用People.map
then I'm using people.map.
确实，第2行确实有一个名为getId的名称。
And it's true that the line 2 definitely does have a name in it called getId.
但是如果你不厌其烦地做第一行，你猜怎么着，
But if you went to the trouble to do line 1, guess what,
实际上，做函数声明的字符更少。
it's actually fewer characters to do the function declaration.
为什么你要费这么大的劲，特别是如果你用常量的话，
Why do you go to all the trouble especially by the way if you use a const,
还有两个字符长。
it's two more characters long.
如果你计算一下，你实际上花了同样多或更多的字符
If you do the math, you're actually spending as much or more characters
以这种方式定义函数，而不是将其作为函数声明。
to define the function that way, rather than doing it as a function declaration.
所以我就是看不出人们为什么被困在这个上面，除了几乎
So I just don't see any reason why people are stuck on this,other than almost
对这个想法的情感依恋，我们可以写出更简洁的代码。
an emotional attachment to this idea that we can write more concise code.
猜猜怎么着，更简洁的代码并不自动等同于更具可读性的代码。
Guess what, more concise code does not automatically equal more readable code.
在某些情况下，它是这样的，但在其他许多情况下，它不是这样的。
In some cases, it does, but in many other cases, it doesn't.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：所以我对Arrow的看法非常不受欢迎
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So there's my really super unpopular opinion on arrow
功能，只是一些思考的食物。
functions, just some food for thought.